Harvard College Observatory observations, logs, instrument readings, and calculations: an inventory
Harvard College Observatory observations, logs, instrument readings, and calculations
- Discussion of Measures of Clusters, no. 2., phaedra2474 (Box 270)
- Measures of Clusters, no 3., 1893-12-02/1894-01-08; phaedra2475 (Box 271)
- Measures of Clusters in Perseus; Observations and Magnitudes, 43., 1903; phaedra2476 (Box 271)
- Work on Magnitude Clouds, 1924/1925; phaedra2477 (Box 271)
  Harvia H. Wilson
- Variables in Agl and Sct -- mostly NA plates, 1931/1937; phaedra2478 (Box 271)
  Richard M. Hindiman, Edgar F. Sanborn Jr
- Shorthand notes, 1921/1926; phaedra2479 (Box 271)
  Harlow Shapley
- Cluster in Perseus, Positions and Magnitudes, 42., 1903; phaedra2480 (Box 271)
- Variables in LMC, 1931; phaedra2481 (Box 271)
- Miscellaneous; Variables, 53., 1925; phaedra2482 (Box 271)
- Variables in Car. and Vel., Z., 1945; phaedra2483 (Box 271)
- Measurements at Maria Mitchell, 1945; phaedra2484 (Box 271)
- Work on Spectra, 1921; phaedra2485 (Box 271)
- Miscellaneous Variable Star Work, 15., 1921/1946; phaedra2486 (Box 271)
  Arville Walker
- Tests on 60-inch telescope, 1924/1926; phaedra2487 (Box 271)
- LMC variables - magnitudes, 1931; phaedra2488 (Box 271)
  Natalie Ross
- Sequences in SMC, 1923; phaedra2489 (Box 271)
- Selected Areas 194-195; 197-199, 1935; phaedra2490 (Box 271)
  SG VIII
- Selected Areas 196, 1935; phaedra2491 (Box 271)
  SG VII
- Selected Areads an -60: 188-194. Measures of B series plates, 1935; phaedra2492 (Box 271)
  SG VI
- Selected Areas 177-182, 1935; phaedra2493 (Box 271)
  SG V
- Star Counts on the LMC, phaedra2494 (Box 272)
- Bright Variable Star Survey, Field 8, phaedra2495 (Box 272)
- Measures of Peruvian Pole Star plates, 1901; phaedra2496 (Box 272)
- VSF Variables SA 16, MW 208, Anticenter 601+17.6, 122, 190, phaedra2497 (Box 272)
  L.R. Ford Layzer
- VSF Variables NSF 299, 305, 679, 298, phaedra2498 (Box 272)
  A. Hearn, T.K.
- Positions of Variables around LMC, phaedra2499 (Box 272)
  Margaret Walton Mayall
- Sequences in LMC, phaedra2500 (Box 272)
- Nebulous Objects in MCs, 1953; phaedra2501 (Box 272)
- AM Plate Milky Way Atlas, phaedra2502 (Box 272)
- Clusters in MCs, phaedra2503 (Box 272)
  Harlow Shapley, Virginia McKibben Nail
- Milky Way Borders, phaedra2504 (Box 272)
  Harlow Shapley, J. Sweeney
  Published in Harvard Annals 106#3
- Positions in omega Cen, phaedra2505 (Box 272)
- O-stars, P-Cyngi stars., phaedra2506 (Box 272)
  A
  D. Hoffleit
- Spectra -- eta Car and others., phaedra2507 (Box 272)
  B
- Spectra., phaedra2508 (Box 272)
  C
- Spectral Classification - Bright Stars., phaedra2509 (Box 272)
  D
- Spectral Classification - Bright Stars., phaedra2510 (Box 272)
  E
- Spectral Classification - Bright Stars., phaedra2511 (Box 272)
  F
- Spectral Classification - Bright Stars., phaedra2512 (Box 272)
  G
- Spectral Classification - Bright Stars., phaedra2513 (Box 272)
  H
- Spectral Classification - Bright Stars., phaedra2514 (Box 272)
- Spectral Classification - Bright Stars., phaedra2515 (Box UNK)
  J
- Spectral Classification - Bright Stars., phaedra2516 (Box UNK)
  K
- Spectral Classification - Bright Stars., phaedra2517 (Box UNK)
  L
- Miscellaneous., phaedra2518 (Box UNK)
  M
- Henrietta Swan Leavitt Notebooks, 1904-04-30/1906-02-19; phaedra2519 (Box 273)
- Variable Stars in Nebulous Regions, 1904-09-20/1905-02-14; phaedra2520 (Box 273)
- The Small Magellanic Cloud. (also Examinations of NSC 6960, 6992), 1905-01-25/1907-02-04; phaedra2521 (Box 273)
- Measures of Comparison Stars. Small Magellanic Cloud, 1905-04-11/1906-01-30; phaedra2522 (Box 273)
- Measurements of Position Magellanic, 1905-05-24/1907-11-23; phaedra2523 (Box 273)
- The Large Magellanic Cloud, 1905-08-30/1921-08-11; phaedra2524 (Box 273)
- Henrietta Swan Leavitt Notebooks, 1905-10-20/1921-08-29; phaedra2525 (Box 273)
- The Small Magellanic Cloud. Observations of Variables, 1905-10-25/1920-08-17; phaedra2526 (Box 273)
- Measures of Comparison Stars. Small Magellanic Cloud, 1906-01-20/1907-05-20; phaedra2527 (Box 273)
- Measurements of Position, 1906-01-29/1907-03-15; phaedra2528 (Box 273)
- Measurements of Position: Glass Plate ruled in millimeters, 1906-02-19/1909-04-06; phaedra2529 (Box 273)
- Standard Magnitudes, 1911-01-07/1914-03-27; phaedra2530 (Box 273)
- Objects looked up by Request; Also Miscellaneous Objects, 1918-01-12/1921-10-14; phaedra2531 (Box 273)